Tikki, I don't get it!
The enigma translated by Master Fu means nothing at all...
That’s normal!
Its meanings are hidden on purpose to
protect the secret of our magical powers
Okay but what about the fact that even I,
the guardian of the Miraculous, can’t understand.
Master Fu took time to find out too!
I know you’ll discover the secret soon, after all...
you helped him with the aquatic one!
You’re right, I’m not gonna give up!
What are you doing?
Nadia: The city of paris is preparing to celebrate Prince Ali's birthday-
Alec: An exclusive report about Adrien's life..
Marinette: *Gasp* Adrien!
Reporter: We were able to follow the daily life of the famous model
Vincent: Perfect! Stunning! I need a smile more.. Al Dente!
A rank dragon degrades a rank dragon (x2)
Sarah: Not Bad, but do u think that you can do it a little more like.. orange?
Mari: *sigh* He really has an amazing life!
Adrien: Ugh.. What an endless day!
Plagg: Without a lunch break even! It's unbearable
Adrien: Here, I'm finally free!
Plagg, Claws Out!
Plagg: What? Ohh noooo
CatNoir: Bugaboo?
"Ladybug here, leave a msg"
CatNoir: Hello Bugaboo, well I'm here on time as usual.. loyal to the post!
It's time for our patrol.. you didn't forget right?
"no msgs but do not forget my cheese"
CatNoir: What could she be doing?!
"Ladybug here, leave a msg"
Maybe now that you're the miraculous guardian, you've more important things to do..
but you know it's okay, I'm the cat for the job!
I'm starting without you, see you soon I hope, let me know.
Kids: What? It's ChatNoir! ChatNoir! ChatNoir!
CatNoir: I'll finally be able to stretch my legs!
Kids: ChatNoir!
Thank you so much!
CatNoir: In your service
"no msgs but do not forget my cheese"
*whistling*
So Mister Banana tell me, you have punch,
the peach, the banana, you understand?
Don’t worry, forget it.
Oh Mister Ramier, it's been a while that you haven’t been akumatised.
You don't miss it a bit, being Mr. Pigeon? Don’t you feel a bit sad, desperate, angry, annoyed maybe?
Even a little disturbed?
Thank you for worrying about it Cat Noir
but I’m in an excellent mood lately!
Oh, so I’ll go.
Say hello to dear Ladybug from me!
Of course... If I see her one day.
No messages but don’t forget my cheese.
A glass of milk as usual mister Cat Noir?
mhm!
How is dear Ladybug, she isn't making much
of an appearance at the moment…
Yeah,  it's particularly calm these days.
This bag was my life Sabrina and you find the way to lose it!
It’s no longer worth talking to me. Understand?
But- Chloé-
Shhh, you shut  up now.
But- Shut- and-  Shut! Shut! Shut!
Not a word. And I forbid you to look at me.
HIDE YOUR EYES.
(Gasp) huh-
It smells like akumatisation!
Oh- Oh- my bag!
What an idiot! You couldn’t say that it was here!?
But I was not allowed to speak, Chloe...
And it’s always the case! But- Shut!
Oh-oh!
On second thought, I will take a double milk.
No messages but don’t forget my chee-
Here's ladybug! Leave a message!
Hello again, bugaboo.
Do you know who this is? It’s the one you stood up- huh?
YES! To never weaken, mother!
I learned the lesson well!
And never let-
yourself be surprised.
Apply these principles to fencing if you want to be better than Adrien Agreste!
Adrien? Don’t worry mother.
I have everything I need to succeed!
End of the patrol bugaboo!
Claws out.
On you forget it exists so much else,
and it’s a new variety, it might be a good surprise!
Miss Kagami Tsurugi called to signal that your
fencing class’s schedule changed again.
It will be an hour early.
Ah, thank you, Nathalie
What are you hiding again, Kagami?
Those schedule changes imposed by the Agrestes are exhausting! But make the most of it to do one extra hour of Russian!
Yes mother
Those schedule changes imposed by the Tsurugis are exhausting!
Once you're home, don’t forget to try the
outfit that I’ve just finished for your next photoshoot
Of course, father
Hmmm? Kagami?? Adrien?? Your fencing class starts in 1 hour and Mr. D’Argencourt is not here yet!
OH! Really? And here I was sure of noting the right schedule this time!
I’m sorry but you can’t-
Stay here alone in school!
No problem M. Aprel. We’ll come back in 1 hour.
But what are you going to do, Kagami?
The art room?
But why did you bring me here?
I never told anyone.
But, I’m passionate about drawing.
And I always have been
Art never lies, poses people do always reflect their personalities
But my mom doesn't let me draw, she thinks I'm not good enough…
You are incredibly talented Kagami!
Really? You think so?
Mhm!
Make a pose for me, I would like to draw you
What pose do you want me to make?
A pose that you feel comfortable with
You know, I admire alot Toulause Lautreck,
I would like to draw you just like the characters he used to paint
Did you know that sometimes he used to sign his drawings with an ideogram?
In Japanese?
Ugh, I'm redoing it, this is not you.
Can I see it?
Make another pose.
It's easy to make a beautiful art of you since you're beautiful, but I wanna draw the real you, what you are in the inside.
No… Still not you. Change your pose
These are model poses, try something more natural, more like you!
Hmm… What do you think of CAT!
Uhh no.. uhmm… I mean, do you prefer… this pose??
No, this is absolutely not natural.
Yes it is, I promise, this is really me!
NO! This is you when you're acting like a clown!
But maybe when I act like a clown… it’s really me..
That way, that’s who you really are.
But.. are you sure?
Yes, you are.. Perfect.
Seems like it’s really time for fencing lessons now.
Ready?
Set!
Go!
Touché
En garde..
Uh, sorry I forgot something in the locker room
It’s time for our patrol!
You didn't forget right?
BOO!
Cat Noir?
(AAHHHH) I talked to him, and oh?
Won’t you stop with your stupid jokes, I could have hurt you!
M’lady, the only thing that hurts...
It's the fact of you leaving me on patrol alone...
I even missed your angry little looks.
I'm a sorry kitten. I'm very busy nowadays...
You amaze me, guardian of the miraculous,
with great title comes great responsibilities!
I promise I won't forget our patrols anymore.
Kagami !
I have to go home my father must be worried...
See you tomorrow !
Oh, see you tomorrow everyone !
I forgot something in class, I'll call you later!
Tatsu, go.
Great! Yeah!
Ah, and I filmed it all dude, this concert was just great!
Not really Nino, I completely missed the intro..
No problem, we can do it again, Adrien..
Yes! We're going to play the song again!
Adrien, it's time..
Five little minutes?
Well, I’ll do better next time, promise
See you tommorow guys!
Weird, The cars are not here yet
It’s a shame, we could have replayed the song
But at least that gives us a little more time together
Don’t worry, we’ll have enough time together especially that we’re going to Prince Ali’s birthday together
I meant only us two
You know, I’m so happy with you.
I think that we’re very similar
Do you feel the same way? Do you also...
Uh.. sorry I thought that there was a wasp
Do you love me, as well?
You were saying?
Adrien... What’s the matter?
I’ve lost something on the boat when my bag fell, don’t wait for me
See you at the birthday party!
Tatsu, Take me to the town hall
I still hope we’ll be going to the prince’s birthday, it’s always a big ceremony where they get the best cheese
For now Ladybug needs me
PLAGG, CLAWS OUT!
Cat Noir, HawkMoth merged his powers with those of the peacock to become ShadowMoth.
He created a supervillain and a sentimonster at the same time. Come quickly!
You will now have to tell the truth to all questions you’ll be asked. I’ll start, who are you, Ladybug?
I.. Am-
A very good swimmer!
Dear Prince Ali, in the name of the city of Paris and its inhabitants, I wish you a happy birthday.
Didn’t I agree with Gabriel Agreste that you would come with his son?
Oh uh... He’s here, mother, he’s answering questions from journalists, I’ll be back.
Ahh, M’lady, it’s been a long time since I had so much fun
Haha, if fighting against a villain with three eyes and a giant Monster amuses you...
at this point, I can’t dare to imagine what your daily life looks like
A supervillain, a giant, and Shadowmoth!
Don’t you find this new name more amusing?
He can change his name as much as he wants, we’ll catch him eventually!
You can count on me and my jokes, Buginette
You won’t have to do it for much longer
In truth, I only have so much fun with you, bye Buginette!
Claws in!
Kagami! I didn’t make you wait too long, I hope
And I hope you found what you are looking for. Huuh- On the barge!
On the barge... of course, yes yes I found it! Thank you.
What was it? Ohh it’s this little lucky charm that Marinette gave it to me for uhh- no I lost it, again!
Are you talking about this?
Listen, I lied too, I lied to my mother so that we could see each other,
I even lied to her that you came with me tonight,
I lied during every fencing class so I can spend more time with you!
Do you see? We are both liars, the difference is that I lie just to be with you.
You! You lie to not be with me
Kagami!
I’d rather be alone.
It only takes one lie to ruin the confidence!
And what if in the end all is lies in our world?
Fly away my little akuma, and blackened this unhappy heart
Lies!
I’m Shadow Moth, I give you the power to rid the world of liars
In return, you must give me the Ladybug and Cat Noir's Miraculous.
Do you give me your word?
You can trust me. No lie will be tolerated, Shadow Moth!
Oh!
Nooo…
This is all my fault… I have to save Kagami!
Plagg Claws out!
Oh, Prince Ali, one more year is to be celebrated but you are still Rock and Roll in your head!
"Applause and Roar"
In the name of the law, what is that!
I'm Lies!
have you ever lied to Officer Roger?
Of course not! A policeman never lies.
You lie, officer Roger!
Aaaah
And you Mother? Have you ever lied?
Kagami!
I don't permit you!
"Aaaaah"
"Gasps"
Kaga… Lie stop this now !
Oh but here is a new candidate for the lie detector test.
I am not lying to you when I tell you that I will free you from Shadow Moth!
Me I will help him, yeah!
Don't stay here Jagged.
I fear nothing, I'm an artist. I still hold to my fans.
It's wrong, you lie to them about your age!
Oh, that's not Rock and Roll! You're...
A world without lies would no longer need superheroes at Noir.
Catacly…
No, If you touch the sphere you will be paralyzed.
Unless you've never lied.
Yes, but is it the case?
Uh not really...
What about you?
Of course not kitty!
We have to lie, even just to keep our identities a secret!
And if we touch this sphere, nothing will be able to stop it from annihilating Paris!
Okay, but what do we do then?
Lucky Charm!
I can't wait to know what you're going to do with a drone
Okay, we can't go inside. This device has never lied before, which means...
Make diversion whilst I send our flying spy!
Let's keep in contact
Your wish is my command m'lady. If I lie I'll go to hell ~
Youhouuu my name's not Chat Noir!
I am not a superhero!
I hate Ladybug!
And I think that ShadowMoth could've called himself PanFly! It's funnier!
Oh yes, I was about to forget: my favorite dish is cabbage with white sauce!
Yummy!
Catch that lying cat, and grab his miraculous!
I won't go back on my words ShadowMoth,
liars always end up paying for their mistakes!
I know what the akumatized object is
Amazing! Break it then!
I don't how to do it without touching it
You're right, only someone who's never lied could infiltrate the sphere to do it, but such a person doesn't exist!
Of course, it exists Chat Noir, it really does!! Fang, Jagged Stone's crocodile!
It's an animal, it doesn't know how to lie!
Great thinking!
Yes! It's working!
Civilians : Heeeelp!
If Lies sees it coming, we’re screwed.
There are only two more liars left in Paris, and one of them knows how to turn his attention.
No, wait doesn’t do that, and what if I’m mistaken?
You know what? I trust you.
Cat Noir no! Don’t do that! You’re crazy!
Yes, crazy for you M’lady.
No, you’re just crazy unconscious.
It is the moment of truth. Take Cat Noir’s Miraculous and then it will be Ladybug’s turn.
Hurry up!
No!
No more evil-doing for you, little Akuma.
Time to de-evilize.
Gotcha!
Bye-bye, little butterfly.
Miraculous Ladybug!
Seriously you need to stop doing this to me!
Yes, but it’s because I find that angry look of yours absolutely irresistible.
Pound it!
Plagg, claws in.
Ah, Ladybug.
Oh how romantic that is, I mean I understand you even though I love every cheese, I always come back to my favorite, camembert.
On guard. Ready. Go
Ouch hey!
Is enough!
It's a fencing lesson here, not a personal problem-solving.
Cease it!
I'm sorry for hurting you Kagami.
And you know all the good times we shared
It was not lies
I know
I know you are hiding something
But I also know there is sincerity in you
So we can't be friends?
How can you trust someone who lied to you?
When I'm ready to see you again, I'll let you know.
Do you know what the difference is, between us and the rest of the world M’Lady?
We can't be completely honest with each other
We have our secrets and sometimes we have to lie
But we know we can trust each other